Terrence Jenkins

(985) 288-7041

terrence_jenkins@yahoo.com

Available for employment on March 01 2020

Summary of Qualifications

Highly skilled, performance driven Aircraft Specialist (2A2X2), exceptional trainer of multiple employees with more than 2.5 years of experience in the world of maintenance, aviation, support, asset management and documentation. Provide safe, reliable, exceptional maintenance, troubleshooting and logistics support for over \$700M of government assets with the United States Air Forces Largest Helicopter maintenance squadron. Trained in Integrated Maintenance Data Collection Systems (IMDS) and Time Compliance Technical Orders (TCTO) for HH-60G Pavehawk Helicopters. Currently possess a DoD Secret Security Clearance.

Areas of Expertise:

•	Electrical & Wiring	☐ Attention to Detail	☐ Troubleshooting
•	Environmental Systems	☐ Drawings/Schematics	☐ Communication/Navigation
•	Technical Manuals	☐ Wire Harness Fabrication	☐ Hydraulic Systems
•	Documentation Microsoft Office Suite	☐ Communication Security	☐ Aerospace Ground Equipment Operation

Professional Experience

Integrated Instrument Flight Control Systems Journeyman

United States Air Force, Nellis AFB, NVAug 2017 - Feb 2020

- Fully qualified and completely proficient on all Avionics tasks with over 2.5 years of Guidance and Controls experience.
- Perform scheduled/unscheduled maintenance on Instrument and Flight Control/Communication Navigation and Electronic Counter Measure Systems on HH-60G Helicopter in the United States Air Force.
- Isolate/repair systems faults, performs inspections, interprets engineering drawings, technical data and completes operational checks using special test equipment.
- Accomplish Time Compliance Technical Orders (TCTOs); inspect/validate system upgrade/modifications and analyze complex technical anomalies on aircraft.
- My goal is also to provide safe, reliable and exceptional maintenance, while ensuring aircraft stay fully
 mission capable and complete their training in a timely manner.

Chick-Fil-A Team Member

Chick-Fil-A, Slidell, LAJan 2015 - July 2017

- Coordinated and assisted in placing special orders from large-scale events such as weddings and birthday events.
- Ensured facility exceeded customers, leadership and health inspectors' expectations.

- Prepared cooking supplies, ingredients and workstations when opening and closing the kitchen in a high paced work environment.
- Took initiative to learn all roles of the job to produce maximum efficiency when short staffed and busy at peak hours.

Education

College of Southern Nevada, Las Vegas, NV – Currently pursuing Bachelors of Science in Graphic Design and Media

Integrated Instrument Flight Control Systems Field Training Detachment, Nellis AFB, NV – Jun 2019 Guidance and Control Systems – Technical School, Sheppard AFB, TX - Jan 2018 - Mar 2018 Electronic Principles Course Technical Training School, Sheppard AFB, TX – Nov 2017 – Jan 2018 Salmen High School, Slidell, LA - Jun 2017

References

- SSgt.Chase Bond

+1 (727) 288-365

chase.bond@us.af.mil

Intergrated Instruments And Flight Controls Craftsman

- SSgt. Joseph Ziegler

+1 (702) 280-043

joseph.ziegler@us.af.mil

Intergrated Instruments and Flight Controls Craftsman

-Will provide additional references upon request.